{
    "kindergarten": {
      "Math": {
        "Counting": [
          {
            "question": "How many apples are there?",
            "options": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
            "answer": "3"
          },
          {
            "question": "What comes after 4?",
            "options": ["3", "5", "6", "4"],
            "answer": "5"
          },
          {
            "question": "How many fingers are on one hand?",
            "options": ["4", "5", "6", "7"],
            "answer": "5"
          },
          {
            "question": "How many legs does a cat have?",
            "options": ["2", "3", "4", "6"],
            "answer": "4"
          },
          {
            "question": "How many days are in a week?",
            "options": ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
            "answer": "7"
          },
          {
            "question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
            "options": ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            "answer": "3"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 1 + 1?",
            "options": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
            "answer": "2"
          },
          {
            "question": "How many wheels does a bicycle have?",
            "options": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
            "answer": "2"
          },
          {
            "question": "How many eyes does a human have?",
            "options": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
            "answer": "2"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 10 minus 5?",
            "options": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
            "answer": "5"
          }
        ],
        "Shapes": [
          {
            "question": "What shape has 3 sides?",
            "options": ["Circle", "Square", "Triangle", "Rectangle"],
            "answer": "Triangle"
          },
          {
            "question": "What shape has 5 vertices?",
            "options": ["Diamond", "Octagon", "Hexagon", "Pentagon"],
            "answer": "Pentagon"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which shape is round?",
            "options": ["Square", "Circle", "Triangle", "Hexagon"],
            "answer": "Circle"
          },
          {
            "question": "How many sides does a square have?",
            "options": ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
            "answer": "4"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the shape of a pizza?",
            "options": ["Square", "Rectangle", "Circle", "Triangle"],
            "answer": "Circle"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which shape has no sides?",
            "options": ["Triangle", "Circle", "Rectangle", "Square"],
            "answer": "Circle"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the shape of an egg?",
            "options": ["Oval", "Triangle", "Square", "Circle"],
            "answer": "Oval"
          },
          {
            "question": "What shape has equal sides?",
            "options": ["Rectangle", "Square", "Circle", "Triangle"],
            "answer": "Square"
          },
          {
            "question": "What shape has 4 vertices and 4 equal sides?",
            "options": ["Square", "Triangle", "Pentagon", "Hexagon"],
            "answer": "Square"
          },
          {
            "question": "What shape is a stop sign?",
            "options": ["Square", "Triangle", "Octagon", "Hexagon"],
            "answer": "Octagon"
          }
        ],
        "Patterns": [
          {
            "question": "Red, Blue, Red, Blue, Red, ___.",
            "options": ["Red", "Blue", "Green", "Purple"],
            "answer": "Blue"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which one does not belong to the pattern? Car, bike, bus, apple",
            "options": ["Bike", "Apple", "Car", "Bus"],
            "answer": "Apple"
          },
          {
            "question": "Circle, Square, Circle, Square, ___.",
            "options": ["Circle", "Square", "Triangle", "Hexagon"],
            "answer": "Circle"
          },
          {
            "question": "1, 2, 3, 1, 2, ___.",
            "options": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
            "answer": "3"
          },
          {
            "question": "Sun, Moon, Sun, Moon, ___.",
            "options": ["Sun", "Moon", "Star", "Cloud"],
            "answer": "Sun"
          },
          {
            "question": "Dog, Cat, Dog, Cat, ___.",
            "options": ["Dog", "Cat", "Bird", "Fish"],
            "answer": "Dog"
          },
          {
            "question": "1, 3, 5, 1, 3, ___.",
            "options": ["1", "3", "5", "7"],
            "answer": "5"
          },
          {
            "question": "Red, Yellow, Red, Yellow, ___.",
            "options": ["Red", "Yellow", "Blue", "Green"],
            "answer": "Red"
          },
          {
            "question": "Car, Bike, Car, Bike, ___.",
            "options": ["Car", "Bike", "Bus", "Truck"],
            "answer": "Car"
          },
          {
            "question": "Circle, Circle, Square, Circle, Circle, ___.",
            "options": ["Square", "Circle", "Triangle", "Hexagon"],
            "answer": "Square"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Science": {
        "Plants": [
          {
            "question": "What do plants need to grow?",
            "options": ["Water", "Oil", "Sand", "Rocks"],
            "answer": "Water"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which part of the plant is green?",
            "options": ["Root", "Leaf", "Stem", "Flower"],
            "answer": "Leaf"
          }

        ]
      },      
      "English": {
        "Letter Recognition": [
          {
            "question": "Which letter comes after A?",
            "options": ["B", "C", "D", "E"],
            "answer": "B"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the first letter of 'Apple'?",
            "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
            "answer": "A"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which letter comes before C?",
            "options": ["A", "B", "D", "E"],
            "answer": "B"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the last letter of the alphabet?",
            "options": ["X", "Y", "Z", "A"],
            "answer": "Z"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is a vowel?",
            "options": ["B", "C", "A", "D"],
            "answer": "A"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the first letter of 'Banana'?",
            "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
            "answer": "B"
          },
          {
            "question": "What comes after X?",
            "options": ["Y", "Z", "A", "B"],
            "answer": "Y"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is a consonant?",
            "options": ["E", "I", "O", "B"],
            "answer": "B"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the first letter of 'Dog'?",
            "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
            "answer": "D"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the first letter of 'Cat'?",
            "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
            "answer": "C"
          }
        ]
      },
      "Social": {
        "Alphabet": [
          {
            "question": "Which letter comes after A?",
            "options": ["B", "C", "D", "E"],
            "answer": "B"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which letter comes after A?",
            "options": ["B", "C", "D", "E"],
            "answer": "B"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which letter comes after A?",
            "options": ["B", "C", "D", "E"],
            "answer": "B"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which letter comes after A?",
            "options": ["B", "C", "D", "E"],
            "answer": "B"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which letter comes after A?",
            "options": ["B", "C", "D", "E"],
            "answer": "B"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which letter comes after A?",
            "options": ["B", "C", "D", "E"],
            "answer": "B"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which letter comes after A?",
            "options": ["B", "C", "D", "E"],
            "answer": "B"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which letter comes after A?",
            "options": ["B", "C", "D", "E"],
            "answer": "B"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which letter comes after A?",
            "options": ["B", "C", "D", "E"],
            "answer": "B"
          },         
          {
            "question": "What is the first letter of 'Apple'?",
            "options": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
            "answer": "A"
          }

        ]
      }
    },
    "grade1": {
      "Math": {
        "Addition": [
          {
            "question": "What is 2 + 3?",
            "options": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
            "answer": "5"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 4 + 1?",
            "options": ["2", "3", "5", "6"],
            "answer": "5"
          }

        ]
      },
      "Science": {
        "Plants": [
          {
            "question": "What do plants need to grow?",
            "options": ["Water", "Oil", "Sand", "Rocks"],
            "answer": "Water"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which part of the plant is green?",
            "options": ["Root", "Leaf", "Stem", "Flower"],
            "answer": "Leaf"
          }

        ]
      }

    },
    "grade3": {
      "Math": {
        "Multiplication": [
          {
            "question": "What is 2 + 3?",
            "options": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
            "answer": "5"
          },
          {
            "question": "What is 4 + 1?",
            "options": ["2", "3", "5", "6"],
            "answer": "5"
          }

        ]
      }


    },

      "grade4": {
        "Math": {
          "Multiplication": [
            {
              "question": "What is 23 Ã— 45?",
              "options": ["1,55", "1,25", "1,45", "1,35"],
              "answer": "1,35"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 56 Ã— 32?",
              "options": ["1,762", "1,872", "1,792", "1,682"],
              "answer": "1,792"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 78 Ã— 24?",
              "options": ["1,862", "1,872", "1,782", "1,952"],
              "answer": "1,872"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 41 Ã— 23?",
              "options": ["963", "953", "943", "933"],
              "answer": "943"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 67 Ã— 21?",
              "options": ["1,377", "1,407", "1,427", "1,387"],
              "answer": "1,407"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 89 Ã— 12?",
              "options": ["1,048", "1,078", "1,068", "1,088"],
              "answer": "1,068"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 34 Ã— 52?",
              "options": ["1,768", "1,748", "1,788", "1,728"],
              "answer": "1,768"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 25 Ã— 47?",
              "options": ["1,185", "1,195", "1,165", "1,175"],
              "answer": "1,175"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 63 Ã— 34?",
              "options": ["2,132", "2,142", "2,152", "2,162"],
              "answer": "2,142"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 81 Ã— 19?",
              "options": ["1,549", "1,539", "1,519", "1,529"],
              "answer": "1,539"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 7 Ã— 312?",
              "options": ["2,194", "2,174", "2,184", "2,164"],
              "answer": "2,184"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 8 Ã— 214?",
              "options": ["1,712", "1,722", "1,742", "1,732"],
              "answer": "1,712"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 9 Ã— 146?",
              "options": ["1,304", "1,334", "1,324", "1,314"],
              "answer": "1,314"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 6 Ã— 453?",
              "options": ["2,738", "2,728", "2,718", "2,708"],
              "answer": "2,718"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 8 Ã— 238?",
              "options": ["1,934", "1,924", "1,904", "1,914"],
              "answer": "1,904"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 7 Ã— 305?",
              "options": ["2,155", "2,145", "2,135", "2,125"],
              "answer": "2,135"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 5 Ã— 432?",
              "options": ["2,140", "2,160", "2,150", "2,170"],
              "answer": "2,160"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 6 Ã— 213?",
              "options": ["1,288", "1,278", "1,258", "1,268"],
              "answer": "1,278"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 7 Ã— 148?",
              "options": ["1,066", "1,056", "1,046", "1,036"],
              "answer": "1,036"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 5 Ã— 324?",
              "options": ["1,620", "1,610", "1,630", "1,640"],
              "answer": "1,620"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 23 Ã— 7?",
              "options": ["171", "151", "161", "181"],
              "answer": "161"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 18 Ã— 4?",
              "options": ["74", "72", "68", "76"],
              "answer": "72"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 16 Ã— 5?",
              "options": ["70", "90", "80", "85"],
              "answer": "80"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 21 Ã— 3?",
              "options": ["53", "83", "73", "63"],
              "answer": "63"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 19 Ã— 2?",
              "options": ["40", "39", "36", "38"],
              "answer": "38"
            }
          ]
        }
      },
    
    
    
    
    
      "grade7": {
        "Math": {
          "Adding Integers": [
            {
              "question": "What is 5 + 3?",
              "options": ["8", "7", "6", "9"],
              "answer": "8"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -7 + 10?",
              "options": ["3", "5", "2", "6"],
              "answer": "3"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -4 + (-6)?",
              "options": ["-8", "-10", "-4", "-12"],
              "answer": "-10"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 12 + (-8)?",
              "options": ["4", "3", "5", "6"],
              "answer": "4"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -15 + 8?",
              "options": ["-7", "-5", "7", "5"],
              "answer": "-7"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -3 + 9?",
              "options": ["6", "12", "3", "-3"],
              "answer": "6"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 7 + (-2)?",
              "options": ["5", "9", "10", "8"],
              "answer": "5"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -8 + 15?",
              "options": ["7", "5", "6", "10"],
              "answer": "7"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -10 + 4?",
              "options": ["-14", "-6", "6", "10"],
              "answer": "-6"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 9 + (-12)?",
              "options": ["-3", "21", "5", "3"],
              "answer": "-3"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 8 + (-5)?",
              "options": ["3", "5", "4", "2"],
              "answer": "3"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -6 + 7?",
              "options": ["1", "3", "2", "4"],
              "answer": "1"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -2 + (-7)?",
              "options": ["-9", "-5", "-7", "-3"],
              "answer": "-9"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 4 + (-11)?",
              "options": ["-7", "1", "-5", "-4"],
              "answer": "-7"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -3 + 6?",
              "options": ["3", "2", "4", "5"],
              "answer": "3"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 10 + (-6)?",
              "options": ["5", "4", "6", "7"],
              "answer": "4"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -9 + 5?",
              "options": ["-4", "4", "2", "0"],
              "answer": "-4"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 11 + (-9)?",
              "options": ["2", "5", "6", "7"],
              "answer": "2"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -2 + 10?",
              "options": ["8", "6", "7", "5"],
              "answer": "8"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 3 + (-7)?",
              "options": ["-4", "2", "6", "5"],
              "answer": "-4"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -5 + 4?",
              "options": ["-1", "0", "-2", "1"],
              "answer": "-1"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 6 + (-6)?",
              "options": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
              "answer": "0"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -8 + 8?",
              "options": ["0", "1", "-1", "-2"],
              "answer": "0"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 7 + (-14)?",
              "options": ["-7", "1", "2", "3"],
              "answer": "-7"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -5 + (-5)?",
              "options": ["-10", "-12", "-15", "-20"],
              "answer": "-10"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 2 + (-9)?",
              "options": ["-7", "-5", "-8", "-9"],
              "answer": "-7"
            }
          ],
          "Multiplying Integers": [
            {
              "question": "What is 3 Ã— -4?",
              "options": ["12", "-12", "7", "-7"],
              "answer": "-12"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -2 Ã— -5?",
              "options": ["-10", "10", "4", "-4"],
              "answer": "10"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -6 Ã— 3?",
              "options": ["-18", "18", "3", "-3"],
              "answer": "-18"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 7 Ã— -2?",
              "options": ["14", "-14", "5", "-5"],
              "answer": "-14"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -5 Ã— -5?",
              "options": ["25", "-25", "10", "-10"],
              "answer": "25"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -4 Ã— 6?",
              "options": ["-24", "24", "-10", "10"],
              "answer": "-24"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 8 Ã— -3?",
              "options": ["-24", "24", "-10", "10"],
              "answer": "-24"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -7 Ã— -6?",
              "options": ["42", "-42", "49", "-49"],
              "answer": "42"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 9 Ã— -4?",
              "options": ["-36", "36", "16", "-16"],
              "answer": "-36"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -5 Ã— 7?",
              "options": ["35", "-35", "50", "-50"],
              "answer": "-35"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 4 Ã— -8?",
              "options": ["-32", "32", "-24", "24"],
              "answer": "-32"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -3 Ã— -9?",
              "options": ["27", "-27", "20", "-20"],
              "answer": "27"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -2 Ã— -4?",
              "options": ["8", "-8", "4", "-4"],
              "answer": "8"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 6 Ã— -3?",
              "options": ["-18", "18", "12", "-12"],
              "answer": "-18"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -5 Ã— -8?",
              "options": ["40", "-40", "20", "-20"],
              "answer": "40"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 12 Ã— -3?",
              "options": ["-36", "36", "-72", "72"],
              "answer": "-36"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 7 Ã— -6?",
              "options": ["-42", "42", "35", "-35"],
              "answer": "-42"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 10 Ã— -9?",
              "options": ["-90", "90", "-100", "100"],
              "answer": "-90"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -11 Ã— -5?",
              "options": ["55", "-55", "60", "-60"],
              "answer": "55"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -4 Ã— -6?",
              "options": ["24", "-24", "20", "-20"],
              "answer": "24"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 8 Ã— -5?",
              "options": ["-40", "40", "-30", "30"],
              "answer": "-40"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 7 Ã— -2?",
              "options": ["-14", "14", "-20", "20"],
              "answer": "-14"
            }
          ],
          "Subtracting Integers": [
            {
              "question": "What is 7 - 3?",
              "options": ["4", "5", "6", "3"],
              "answer": "4"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -5 - (-8)?",
              "options": ["3", "-3", "13", "-13"],
              "answer": "3"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 4 - (-2)?",
              "options": ["2", "6", "8", "5"],
              "answer": "6"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -10 - 5?",
              "options": ["-5", "-15", "15", "5"],
              "answer": "-15"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -3 - (-9)?",
              "options": ["6", "-6", "3", "-3"],
              "answer": "6"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 5 - (-4)?",
              "options": ["9", "1", "3", "7"],
              "answer": "9"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -8 - (-2)?",
              "options": ["-6", "-10", "6", "10"],
              "answer": "-6"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 3 - 7?",
              "options": ["-4", "10", "4", "-10"],
              "answer": "-4"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -6 - 4?",
              "options": ["-10", "-2", "2", "10"],
              "answer": "-10"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 9 - (-3)?",
              "options": ["12", "6", "3", "-3"],
              "answer": "12"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -4 - 5?",
              "options": ["-9", "9", "7", "-7"],
              "answer": "-9"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -3 - (-7)?",
              "options": ["4", "-4", "5", "-5"],
              "answer": "4"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 2 - (-5)?",
              "options": ["7", "-7", "3", "-3"],
              "answer": "7"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 10 - (-2)?",
              "options": ["12", "8", "10", "6"],
              "answer": "12"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -9 - (-6)?",
              "options": ["-3", "-5", "-1", "-7"],
              "answer": "-3"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -3 - 3?",
              "options": ["0", "-6", "-3", "-9"],
              "answer": "-6"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 8 - (-4)?",
              "options": ["12", "4", "8", "10"],
              "answer": "12"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -2 - (-5)?",
              "options": ["3", "-3", "7", "-7"],
              "answer": "3"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 6 - (-6)?",
              "options": ["12", "6", "4", "8"],
              "answer": "12"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -4 - (-2)?",
              "options": ["-2", "-6", "2", "6"],
              "answer": "-2"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is -7 - 4?",
              "options": ["-11", "-3", "7", "3"],
              "answer": "-11"
            },
            {
              "question": "What is 5 - 10?",
              "options": ["-5", "5", "-15", "15"],
              "answer": "-5"
            }
          ]
        }
      },

      
        "grade9": {
          "Math": {
            "Simplifying Polynomials": [
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 3(x + 4)",
                "options": ["3x + 4", "3x + 12", "7x", "x + 7"],
                "answer": "3x + 12"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 5(2x - 3)",
                "options": ["10x - 15", "10x + 15", "7x - 3", "15x - 5"],
                "answer": "10x - 15"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 2(x + 3y)",
                "options": ["2x + 6y", "2x + 3y", "6x + y", "5x + 6y"],
                "answer": "2x + 6y"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: -4(3x - 2)",
                "options": ["-12x + 8", "-12x - 8", "12x + 8", "-12x + 2"],
                "answer": "-12x + 8"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 3x + 5x + 2x",
                "options": ["5x + 2x", "7x", "10x", "9x"],
                "answer": "7x"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 7y - 3y + 5y",
                "options": ["5y", "9y", "15y", "7y"],
                "answer": "9y"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 2x^2 + 3x^2 - x^2",
                "options": ["4x^2", "5x^2", "3x^2", "2x^2"],
                "answer": "4x^2"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 5x + 4x^2 - 3x - 2x^2",
                "options": ["5x + 2x^2", "7x + 2x^2", "2x + 2x^2", "2x^2 + 2x"],
                "answer": "2x + 2x^2"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 2(x + 3) + 4(x - 1)",
                "options": ["6x + 6", "2x + 10", "6x + 2", "2x + 2"],
                "answer": "6x + 2"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 3x + 4x + 5x",
                "options": ["12x", "15x", "10x", "9x"],
                "answer": "12x"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 4x - 2x + 7x",
                "options": ["9x", "5x", "6x", "8x"],
                "answer": "9x"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 3(2x + 4) - 2(3x - 6)",
                "options": ["6x + 12 - 6x + 12", "6x + 12 - 6x - 12", "6x + 12 - 6x + 6", "6x + 12 - 6x - 6"],
                "answer": "24"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 5(3x + 2) + 3(2x - 1)",
                "options": ["15x + 10 + 6x - 3", "15x + 10 + 6x + 3", "15x + 10 + 6x - 6", "15x + 6 + 6x - 3"],
                "answer": "21x + 7"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 2x(x + 4) + 2(x - 3)",
                "options": ["2x^2 + 4x + 2x - 6", "2x^2 + 4x + 2x + 6", "2x^2 + 6x - 6", "2x^2 + 6x + 6"],
                "answer": "2x^2 + 6x - 6"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 7(x - 2) + 3(x + 1)",
                "options": ["7x - 14 + 3x + 3", "7x - 14 + 3x - 3", "7x + 14 + 3x + 3", "7x + 14 + 3x - 3"],
                "answer": "10x - 11"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 4(x - 2) + 3(x + 1)",
                "options": ["7x - 5", "7x - 1", "7x - 7", "7x - 6"],
                "answer": "7x - 5"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 3(x - 1) + 2(2x + 3)",
                "options": ["3x - 3 + 4x + 6", "3x - 3 + 4x - 6", "3x + 3 + 4x + 6", "3x + 3 + 4x - 6"],
                "answer": "7x + 3"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 2x(x - 3) + 3(x + 2)",
                "options": ["2x^2 - 6x + 3x + 6", "2x^2 - 6x + 3x - 6", "2x^2 - 3x + 6", "2x^2 - 3x - 6"],
                "answer": "2x^2 - 3x - 6"
              },
              {
                "question": "Simplify: 2x + 3x - 4x + 5x",
                "options": ["6x", "5x", "7x", "8x"],
                "answer": "6x"
              }
            ]
          }
        }
      
      

    






  }
  